What's up, boss? I'm Ronnie Shen.
Then I'm Michael Costa. This is Sports War, the show where we are legally not allowed to agree with each other.
For example, if I say UFC needs to be more violent...
Oh, well, then I say fighters need to sell a difference as peacefully with a licensed therapist.
Yeah, well, I'd like to introduce you to my two therapists, Sigmund Freud and Carl Jung.
Oh, yeah? Well, I should go to therapy.
See, that's how I'm obsessed with your mom.
Yeah.
Yeah, man, exactly. You need to explore those feelings with a licensed medical professional.
I'll send you some names.
Hey, let's talk golf, okay?
Short game, amateur, handicap, ball washer.
These aren't just Ronnie's nicknames.
They're golf terms.
And this week was a historic one on the links.
Tonight, Rory McAvoy is now one of only six golfers to win all four major golf championships, winning the Masters for the first time.
The kid who grew up in Northern Ireland...
...overcome with emotion, winning his first green jacket, 11 years, after winning his last major championship.
Wow, congrats to Roy McAvoy.
It took him 11 years to get a new green blazer.
And as someone currently serving a 20-year band from the men's warehouse, I can totally relate.
This is totally different, you idiot.
Rory was trying to accomplish one of the hottest things in all of sports.
You just took a dump in a fitting room.
Well, they guaranteed I was going to like the way I looked and breaking a verbal contract has consequences.
The point is, I'm happy for Roy McAvoy.
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm not.
Okay? I don't want to seem happy.
Everyone knows that Irish people are the best when they're depressed.
Haven't you ever read James Joyce?
Hell, no, I'm a Frank McCourt man.
Well, he's Irish American dumbass.
Check your stats, bro.
McCourt was raised in the slums of Limerick and he spoke to the soul of Irish suffering like no man since William Butler Yates, dumbass, which brings to our eyes Irish eyes better than night.
What will make Roy McAvoy cry in public next?
As always, brought to you by gambling.
Gambling.
The only thing you're really addicted to is having a good time.
You're moving on.
The NBA Playoff starts Saturday.
But if you're a little girl with a big imagination like Costa, you also have a reason to be excited.
Move over Ken.
LeBron James is a first male athlete to be part of the new Ken Basseter line.
And Barbie dolls, look at him.
The message on the back of the box says, a true MVP.
Our LeBron James Ken Basseter's doll represents resilience, hope, and pride for the city of Akron.
This is the dumbest toy ever.
I hope it comes of a brony James doll that you'll force to play with even though it sucks.
Well, brawn again, boy, toy.
I happen to love LeBron.
He has every, he has what every little girl wants in a doll.
Pride for the city of Akron.
Now, they can play until their hearts content with a middle-aged man dressed like a 14-year-old no notes.
They should expand this to other NBA legends, like Dennis Rodman, The Worm, The First Doll in Barbie history with the piercable scrotum.
Or my favorite, my favorite from the childhood, Will Chamberlain.
There are hundreds of different Barbies and he can have sex with all of them.
Which brings us to our extremely random endorsement deal Better the Week, presented by Joanne Fabrics.
Which athlete will sign the next extremely random endorsement deal brought to you by Gambley.
Gambley, they're doing amazing things with wheelchair now.
Look, let's go to the diamond.
Baseball is a sport where you have to know your signs, right?
Curveball, pitching change.
I'll take four beers, no tip.
But this week, Bryce Harper took that to the next level.
Philadelphia Philly slugged her Bryce Harper is about to take another swing at Fatherhood.
And he got creative with the babies' baby's gender revealed during last ninths game.
Harper Ashford stopped trade turner to hand him either a bluer-a-pink bat before he went up to head as a gender reveal.
He found out right before he stepped up to the plate that he'll be having a baby boy.
This is awesome.
Baseball needs more medical tests revealed during games.
I want to see a runner slide into home in the Empire of Yells.
You are safe from Tasex disease.
Costner, you're out of your f***ing mind, all right?
This is ruining the game.
You can't be doing gender reveals at the plate.
Gender reveals are supposed to be for a close group of loved ones that you're hoping to injure with explosives.
Ronnie, I got your gender reveal bat right here.
Surprise, it's brown since you're a piece of shit.
Well, costner.
Yeah.
For those of us who've had sex, this is a disaster, all right?
Baseball is the thing you think about when you're not trying to get someone pregnant.
Get your family planning out of my sports, okay?
Can we please see a baseball story that has nothing to do with sex?
The Baltimore Orioles double-a affiliate that chest-of-peak base-ox decided to unveil an alternative team identity to help them gain traction with new audiences.
That included the new alternative name, the Oyster Catchers, along with a brand new logo.
This logo, which at least to many seems to depict a baseball glove catching an Oyster, others interpreted a bit differently.
The team took the criticisms to heart, deleting their unannouncedment within minutes, but later they unveiled a new new logo showing a bird holding a bat.
God dammit.
I'm never going to be able to slip and all you stuff of baseball glove ever again.
And that's the only way I like them.
What are you talking about, Ronnie?
The Oyster logo is great.
If anything, the new logo is the one that's perverted.
That bird is clearly flying away with some guy severed penis.
And you know what? That poor guy.
But those lucky baby birds, what a lunch.
This whole thing just confirms my belief that baseball team should get rid of logos entirely, okay?
If they're not sexualizing oysters that pissing off Native Americans, every team should just name themselves after their city, like a Philadelphia Phillies, the Boston-Bostonese, the Cleveland-Clevelandese, the Detroit-Titties.
Nothing sexual, okay?
I disagree, Ron.
All team names should be sexual, but educational.
Sex ed in this country is a joke.
But if the Philadelphia Philopian tubes play the Cleveland steamers, well now we're learning, which brings us to our four-carat diamond better the week.
What baseball mascot will Ronnie have a dream about tonight?
Brought to you by gambling.
Gambling.
Tons of cultures sleep outside.
All right, that's it for sportswear.
Join us next time when we debate what act of war, Jean-Marant, will should mine for his next celebration.
It's gotta be hitting a nuclear button, man.
I'm gonna hit that button.
This is a draw.